<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts xmlns="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
	<context id="DuplicateElementConsistencyViolation">
		<description>A <b>duplicate element</b> inconsistency indicates that at least two elements with the same MOF id exist in different model partitions. This leads to an inconsistency since MOF ids have to be unique. Otherwise references to model elements cannot be correctly resolved by the MOIN core.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;<b>Root cause and correction</b>&lt;br&gt;The reason for this inconsistency can most probably be found in a version conflict of the existing model partition files. In order to correct the inconsistency, it is recommended to first check if the model partition files come from the same source and release and to exchange or delete the files causing the problem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it is not possible to solve the problem by exchanging or deleting model partitions, the duplicate elements can be deleted using the quick fix option. The quick fix option allows to delete either single elements or all of the duplicate elements except one.</description>
	</context>

	<context id="DanglingLinkConsistencyViolation">
		<description>A <b>dangling link</b> inconsistency indicates a missing element which is referenced by another element.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;<b>Root cause and correction</b>&lt;br&gt;Most probably, the missing element was contained in a model partition that is now missing. To correct the problem, it is recommended to first check if it is possible to restore the missing model partitions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the missing model partition cannot be restored, the link pointing to the missing element can be deleted using the quick fix option. Please note that this can cause further inconsistencies or OCL constraint violations.</description>
	</context>
	<context id ="DuplicateParentConsistencyViolation">
		<description>A <b>duplicate composite parent</b> inconsistency indicates a problem with a contains-association between two elements. Due to the MOF constraints, a component element must not have more than one composite parent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;<b>Root cause and correction</b>&lt;br&gt;The inconsistency is most probably caused by conflicting versions of the existing partition files. To solve the issue, it is recommended to check the consistency of the partition files first.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this does not help, one or more of the links causing the problem can be deleted using the quick fix option.</description>
	</context>
	<context id ="LinkPermissionConsistencyViolation">
		<description>Link permission violation. This consistency violation is raised if a link cannot be resolved because the partition of the element on one end does not have access to the partition of the element at the other end due to permission restrictions, for example by the lifecycle management (DCs).</description>
	</context>
</contexts>
